Yeah
We came for the spark in the black of the night
Stayed for the truth when it bit and it fell right
Laugh in the chaos breathing the strange if you felt something real it means you changed
So keep that flame where your feet used to be
Take it with you
Don't need a throne, don't need permission
Just a sharp little heart and a clearing tuition
If they don't get you, let them stay blind
We don't beg for love, we conjure up
breathe out, hold the line, steal the gate, keep the line
happened last night. Oh, my head. I didn't know what happened last night. I don't know.
Hi, baby. Hey, Trixie. It's crazy. It's fucking crazy. Good morning, Nancy. Thanks for being here.
Bunch of stuff happened last night. I mean, it was almost, it almost went perfect and then it did it.
Good morning. Good morning, Rudy. Hi. How are you? Hi, Nancy. Hi.
I do want to thank Hebs and Zaya. That was, that went pretty good. I think ghosts will
probably never talk to me again. Oopsie. And I did maybe delete a few of the things I posted
last night, but most of it, I was like, that stands.
because I did, without any provocation,
without me ever saying anything,
Bita did say, oh, when you're sitting there crying
about your friend that died, what happened?
Well, it was kind of like, I said, go check out,
go check out Pepsi's zip.
But I was like, they're real nice and be nice to them.
But I was like, you know, I was like,
they're doing open panel and stuff.
You can go check them out and you know we're there and
I'm sorry pepsin they have em and ghosts. I mean I
Don't know you know ghost is you know I was like ghost. I wasn't supposed to be like
Mean or it was supposed to be like, you know, he wanted to hang out somewhere. It's like a milk and pail and stuff
Then he kind of you know, he did what ghost does when a little wild
Mattis I said some shit I regret probably
Damn
I'm sorry ghost
But it wasn't supposed to be anything mean or anything like that to them
Kind of like
You bring
You know people bring their kids to the restaurant and the kids like it starts crying in the middle of dinner at a nice restaurant or something
Like that kind of felt like that a little bit. I was like ghosts. Come on. I was like, chill. I
Don't know
Hey, they put I guess be a patron trying to watch to their life and stuff. I was on for a couple hours. I mean that
Hey Rudy, it went okay. I mean it was just
With I mean, I mean, we're really good with them with the ghost you can't
Man, I didn't say I'm trying to embarrass me to them, too
I
Feel like he almost like won a little bit because I went too far and I went too far. Oh
I got so drunk
I'm gonna stop drinking at like four in the afternoon until midnight because I will say things I regret and stuff. I
Won't forget without probably listen to this. Oh
And then I'll stop talking about her forever this lady beta
First of all someone's in her chat and who it is this guy Tony, right? He's known as Tony and whatever right or
Even if he's known to Benjamin who cares I know his information now
He sent three pizzas last night. He actually sent he kept texting the Domino's people
And a drinking in me the devil. He kept texting the Domino's people. Oh go back to the house
He's gonna hand you the money in the tip to knock on the door again
She was laughing at the press. Oh, yeah
It was the passing of my friend. Yes. She said, oh, oh, oh, you're sad because your friend Danny danger got killed or whatever
She laughed about it. I didn't I didn't bring him up to her ever and she like decided to laugh about that
That
It's not sealed the deal with beta, you know
How dare you bitch? How dare you just leave his name out of your mouth?
Like you didn't know him at all. Okay?
They're gonna be they're a little controversial and stuff, you know, it's it's hey, I am too. Oh look at corn fed hog
Yeah, I know Benjamin Benjamin K. Okay, and I know mr. Cow
In Wisconsin how about you die?
Hey, we haven't given guests in the show. Hey good times
What up?
One second. There you are. Hey, what's up, dude? Yeah, I don't know if you saw but yeah, I mean this shit happened last night
But yeah, that's your cat
She's right there and sitting behind me
Hi, Mrs. Katie is it mr. Or mrs. Her name's porch monkey porch. Okay porch monkey. Hi porch monkey
Hi little porch monkey. This is mr. Rudy and
And pebs and Zaya have a cute dog
I think their dog was like one of the cutest dogs I've ever seen in my life
I didn't know they lived together. I thought there were like I was like I said, I said there were a couple and then they're like
Oh, we're not really a couple. We're just like really close friends that we fucking once in a while
And then it's like you fix the layout so I don't have to sit so much. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry like this
Yeah, okay. I'm sorry about that
Don't be sorry. I hate it when people say sorry. Okay. I'm sorry. Yeah, okay. I'm gonna say it
I don't think I don't think that's true. I don't know about but that and and I know Chris K said his kid
I like Chris K's cat Chris K said look kind of look like mine. I'd yeah
His cat was a cute and I'm so sorry his cat passed away
Can I say something to you? Yes. Have you ever seen?
Be this came up and have her cat sit on her lap before and
Never never never never once never once my life. No, she's not she's not a true kitty person
I mean, her cats walk around on the floor and stuff.
And have you seen the cats?
My cats just jump on my back and like.
I'm not saying she abuses her animals.
I'm not saying, you know, I'm not saying that either,
but it's like she's not that affectionate
in my, that I've ever seen.
I mean, I just.
I guess that was the point I was trying to make.
Yeah.
I mean, I never really thought about it like that, but.
Yeah, I have never seen her hold her cat and never I just seen them walking around the floor and her giving them catnip
And she feeds them well. They have beautiful litter box. They have a little little beautiful home
She's very little bit judgemental about well my ear cats don't have a litter box your cat
You're one of your cats does not fix you keep saying my cats aren't fixed over and over
I'm like one of the male one male cat
Is that a long California for adopt a cat? You have to pay for it to be fixed. I think so
I think so, but I didn't adopt him. He was born here and
And I will get him fixed
Like, um, you know, but he would warn you if you don't really let him outside. You don't have to worry
Yeah, I mean if it's a male cat the thing you gotta worry about male cats. Yeah is
Once you reach maturity, they like to spray to mark their territory.
Yeah, and, you know, he doesn't, I mean, he's a male cat, right?
But he's like, I've had male cats, most of the male cats.
Get to a certain eight and then they want to be go to go wander and she has kind of wandered a little bit
but he always comes back, but
He's more of like a daddy's boy kind of like he stays here at most of the time
He like he doesn't really go and he's right here. You can see him right here on the floor here
Yeah, I mean that's why I let my cats outside because I remember I just like
I didn't have the cat door and stuff and they would just sit and sit in me out at the door
They had cats try to jump out the window and so you live in the city
I live in the city, but it's like it's a beach city and it's kind of like not like
Too industrial. I don't know how to explain it. It's like a little bit of a suburbs kind of feel to it
It's a really am am said you lived in Hollywood
No, I live I don't live in Hollywood as she took me to Hollywood. She drove me to Hollywood
our second day like
It was about an hour away. It's about an hour away and I like that
It's like Allied Master Computer, which is like actually a character from a book called
I have no mouth and I must scream and that's and she kind of relates to that
artificial intelligence crazy computer character and so does the other person who sent me three pizzas last night who beat it was like
when I said his first name and his city or his state not a city I said his first name and his state
she's like I'm gonna be sharing the screenshots with him and stuff all right so it's like I'm gonna
give you a word of advice never show a mo emotional weakness and never talk about people you care about
be I don't well I don't care about them anymore because because these these psychopaths will use
it to try to destroy your emotional well-being okay
yeah I know but and she is I don't think it's you yeah I know I know and I'm and I and sometimes
I do show emotional vulnerability a little bit sometimes sometimes I do
But, you know, I just tell it like it is, and it's like for someone to say to my friend
that just died literally three weeks ago to laugh about that and say, and then get his
name wrong, and his laugh at my face about my friend dying, and then keep pressing me
about this other person, another friend of mine that died, and keep calling him a piece
of trash and loser, and then defending this woman Tracy over about it and stuff, and then
saying I did something wrong to him.
It's it's just wrong to me and it's like I'm like this is just well evil
This is fucking evil like this person is evil that would do that. I wouldn't ever make fun of someone that
It's some you know how many horrible things that have been said or videos made about me
Destroy my psychological mindset. Yeah, and but you're strong mentally. I'm strong mentally. Hey, we're still here
Oh, we're not destroyed. We were not we're not I never seen you cry in the in the bushes or whatever
I never seen myself cry even though I'm setting up
Oh, go cry about it.
Oh, you're crying on your show.
I cried a couple of times in my show when people died.
Oh, yeah, I don't get it.
Real men can cry.
Real men are allowed to have people cry.
Yeah, and it's like, but then it's like,
it has never seen a woman like that.
It's just like, oh my God, you can go cry, bitch.
Like, what's wrong with her?
Yeah, I've heard her cry.
I didn't make fun of her.
I don't know.
It's like, I just get so fraffled.
If she ever lets me out again.
Ain't sure I see a man on there. I'm gonna say the n-word.
Good. I mean, he's, he is, he is. I mean, I've never seen a man.
No, I'm not calling that. I'm saying she has a double standard for people.
Oh, she does. Cause she'll say it. And then she's like, and then I mean,
I've said it on my show. I mean, she was just saying last week,
Oh, here he is, you know, calling Sam and the N word on his show.
And then she's like, well, why would you call?
Why would you say that word on my show? You never would say it on another show.
I said it on my show. You know, I did. And I'll say it on.
I mean, it's just crazy. It's crazy. And I don't want to offend anybody. It's not a racial thing at all. He's not black
I mean, it's like and it's just like well, I I could tell you I
Can tell you one thing I used to hang out in in some of the worst areas Detroit back in the day. Okay? Yeah
And I knew how to respect people. So I'd never got fucking yeah
You didn't get beat up by anybody for saying that word. No, they'll beat you up down there. Shoot your ass. Sure
Well, I've had gangbangers say this is my certain word, right? I don't want to say it on your show. Yeah
But um, I I just laugh. I'm like, yeah, yeah, you're my man or whatever and fuck you. We don't my god
Look who it is. There he is. He's in the chat
You can say it now same good times if you want
I don't know who's in your shot I can't
It's Samman
Samman stop saying the unword
Oh no he can say it my friend was counting the other night he said it a hundred times in less than ten minutes on my show
I was counting the other night sometimes he says it twice in one sentence
Yeah in one sentence this is like
That's the only word in his vocabulary practically he has like ten words he knows that's one of them
But then it's like I say the soft age he get I mean it's some kind of like loophole that he figured out
Oh, look he said it right there. He said no hard R right there
All right, it's like yeah
Listen, I've hung around real niggers before I don't he ever has oh my god. Oh my god
No, no listen
Well, you're baiting me to do it it
I've actually
Hung around in the hoods you try it in some most scary shit you ever seen make a rod turn one time
Just blocks the burden down houses and one one drug dealer on a street corner
Randomly fucking in a starters fucking jacket. Okay
all right hey hey hey guys guys this is gonna be um adult you know this is like uh this is like uh
well you said 18 plus right yeah yeah this is 18 come on hard r soft i can't really tell maybe
you can't say the letter r this is like i've call him i've call him saying the hard r many of times
Yeah, we're having a nice little chat today. I mean, this is a chat. We're bullshitting. Yeah. Hey, have you ever heard of sticks and stones can break your bones? Words can never harm me. I mean, sometimes they do hurt a little bit, but they don't hurt you. They don't physically hurt anybody. And can we all get the adults here and say, Hey, well, I don't I don't like being a double standard for the unword.
No, it's only double standards for who people she doesn't like.
That's still a double standard
Like a triple standard or something you're good. Yeah, and I and Nancy I know is like it is like an ugly word in some contexts
And depending where you are
So I'm gonna respond to that when I was hanging out in the Hoosity, Detroit if you're a white guy down there
And they they use that word they called you that word it meant they respected you
I wasn't done when I say I it's not racist. I'm not yeah because I grew up in the culture where that was normal
Okay, right, right, and it's like in some cultures. There's a word they call each other
F-A-G and that's like bro and basically right
It's like or something or that's kind of moral insult
But I'm saying like I guess it's not clumsy was telling me or someone was saying I guess it was all borrow
He was saying oh, yeah, and in El Salvador they say this it means
you know N word um but then we call it if we if it's somebody some outside are calling us that
it's bad but if it's the if it's like our friend it's like bro right yeah yeah that's what I was
trying to say yeah yeah I'm sorry I didn't interrupt you so no no like you you explain what I was
trying to say so like while I'm in Detroit if um if they called you the N word and your white guy
I don't know. Otherwise, they
would say, get the **** out
here, cracker or. Yeah, you
need up or something, right?
And they wouldn't just. There's
no beating up. There's just
gunshots. Um Pebs take over
soon. Um is you gonna take over
the show? Yeah, I'll let her
I'll let her take over my show
for a day. Pebs and Zia,
they're they were cool to me.
I did send Ghost over there for like,
I'll say it was a little prank,
it was a little prank that I like sent Ghost over there,
but I said, be nice.
And I said, they're good people.
I was like, don't, he wanna, you know,
he likes to, he likes to fight.
And then he like took it too seriously.
And I had to like, you know, show the,
we can't say that, no.
Am I insane?
Not letting them take over?
Oh, you know, they're just, they've been kind to me.
I don't what were you trying to say? You're gonna like re-stream their stream or something. No, they I'll let them
Take over my stream like like they'll let them like, you know
I'll go away to the store or something and they can be in charge if they want to be you know
Well, I already went to the store this morning. I I joined their cult. Yeah, I
Mean I did join the membership because they love I was on for two hours last night
I like ghost on and he kind of like, you know, what ghost does like ghost
Goes too far and he kind of like I said, it's like
For people on my stream anymore like a lot of these people are psychos. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like maybe like, you know, I think they'll I think that they would be fine on it
No, they didn't cry they were they were fine. Um, she actually ghosted art. She already knew who ghost was
And then it's like, he's like, she's like, oh, I, she's like,
I heard, I was on a show with you a year ago
and you were saying this and that.
She already knew who he was.
She has a good memory.
And why are you rolling your eyes, he man?
You're rolling your eyes?
You know, they have the cutest dog.
They're actually a cute couple.
I guess they're not identifying themselves as a couple really.
They're saying we're close friends with benefits
kind of in a way.
But, you know, I had to show the text messages
where I told ghosts.
behave yourself there like like be nice and uh and you know i like them so i said be careful
you're playing with fire it wouldn't be you're dealing with those two okay okay okay well
i'm kind of stupid in a certain way where i just i kind of think he's cute and then he kind of
jokingly with you know but you know he's not I know he's not I know he's not
and I was like are you homophobic and he's like no not at all and stuff to the
stream saying I'm gathering up pray for them wow she's now she thinks I'm
working for wow okay hey you know what but this
But I know of them is just what Alexandra said. I mean other than peps I was on peps with peps
I knew I knew peps before she ever moved in was a
Yeah, I mean I've emitter on her own and then I never met him
But I just wanted to meet him and then he's been on lately with her and
They were just cool. I mean, it's like but
Yeah. Um and Sam and you're on
that show too and you're cool
with them and it's like so if
you're saying there's
something wrong, I mean, what
No, I I'm just saying you like
to play with you like to play
with fire. Yeah, I do but you
know what? I'm a little pyro
mother fucker sometimes. Baby
I'm going to get a putting out
fire. Don't burn your soul too
much. Okay. Good morning, Kate.
Yeah. We have a guest. Let's
I'm gonna say no, I'm just saying nobody's saying nothing. So I say you could go wherever you want. That's it a eat
What?
Right. No, you like it. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. All right, my nigga. So you eat you take it now. Let's go come over here
And we're in three seconds twice. What?
Say you eat you see here. Where? Where did you learn your vocabulary?
Even go to school, right? He said if Fox has already
TTC here. Keep it count
Oh
You can say it with a soft ah
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, good
Next up next time put ETC Higa at the bottom right you the gay ETC Higa. All right, you know what you're a gay ETC Higa, too
So I think it's like I'm out of here. Okay. Bye. I'm gonna say that we're some more and go live good times. Fuck you nigga
Nigger nigger nigger nigger. No. No. No. No. No. Stop stop stop stop stop. Whoa. Don't you I told you there's double standards
I live in York City, I can I can see them
Okay, bye, but what is it but Alexander says I'm gathering souls for them or
Look at Kate. Look Kate mad. Look why I can't that cycle over there. Look. They mad your minds are mad that you go over there
I don't know, I haven't seen them get matchy, man.
I mean, like-
Oh my God, I'm disappointed.
Oh my God, don't go over there.
What a man.
I
You just
Yeah, I gotta eat it now
Yo, I'll get some pears over here
Yeah, hey, and you know what all I don't know is like, you know Alexander slander of them and I miss I know
Alex hey, man, how you doing girl shout to you. He man
Me geez
You dumbass you supporting him now you don't fuck you his mind. Oh, you slow
Okay, get out of here
Okay, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go. I wonder how much cocaine he's already done this morning. Oh my god
He's sounds like a lot a lot a lot a lot
I'm gonna go get Alexander's transcript because you know, she likes to strike channels and stuff
I'm gonna go to transcript and see what she's saying about me and pebs and they are today
Because she's I don't know become obsessed with people like that
It's my nature. I mean, I don't know. It's like I get hyper focused. I know I know I do
I know I have I have a bad obsessed obsessive part of me the promoter of demons
The promoter of demons who harm ch il dr en and the parties of
Um, the rumored PEDO belong together. Okay. I'm 15 minutes long. I'm just gonna cut this out and I put it in the AI
Transfix you know the best way to get rid of her is just ignore I know but I would like to hear what she's had
To say about me because you did why why because you like the negative energy that she brings in your soul
Well, I'm I'm just gonna I'm not bringing playing her her voice, which is like the the transmitter of the energy
I'm just gonna read the transcript and that's gonna be oh my god
I'm getting the transcript. I was gonna see what she had to say about my knee and them marijuana or something
I need marijuana, but I can't afford it this week
Unfortunately, but it's okay. Well, I'm gonna proceed with this
The transcript is being generated right now guys. I'm gonna be reading this a little bit
what's going on with me being mentioned,
saying the promoter of demons who harm, oh, so sick.
She didn't really know anything about Lilith.
I mean, it's like, she, and also this woman, really.
All right, all right, like, do you really know who she is?
I met her in person good times.
Have you met her in person?
No, but she she was talking about how she's a fallen angel. Yeah, and she told me she's a vampire
She told me she's an alien. She told me
She's talking about recently how she's the reincarnation of Adolf Hitler she wants to throw people in oven
And in the oven she wants to throw you and me it's gonna be you and me in that oven good talk
And we're Jews and so is be I mean be that it's I mean it gets crazy. It gets crazy. I mean it's like
what what what if you know somebody's crazy why do you pay attention what they
because it's because what because it's funny to me
I I don't I don't think you think it's funny I think you take
I do this is a channel I need she said she's an alien she said Tommy James is a magical ginger
she said she's a 9000 year old vampire she says she's a pirate I mean it's like every I mean every
Dungeons and Dragons character. I think she is
I mean, good Lord. I mean, a good Lord. It gets so good. Yeah, I
She said she was a devil before too. And she said she's a devil and she's a Christian and a porn star
This is so confusing to me. What the fuck? I mean, and then it's like, oh
It's only gonna make it worse if you give her attention, okay? Okay, but I won't say her name
I'll say am and I'm just
Am show today
All right, folks, good morning, good afternoon, or good evening, whatever time it is, wherever
in the vast world.
I already know what you're talking about.
Welcome once more to another live stream of I Around This Time.
I'm your host, this am.
And hopefully in this live stream, which is audio only, we'll come through.
I'm currently on the road, okay?
And, okay.
Come on.
Faster, faster.
Okay.
Um, and I'm currently on the road life in life
But I did receive a few DMs and emails like from overnight in regards to a certain individual
Who's been promoting a demon worship within the streaming community specifically the worship of a demon known as Lilith
This is known to specifically target and kill babies harm children
Okay, I suppose that's what I'm about to share evolves when the people of rumored PEDO
Com as well, but that shouldn't come surprised as anybody and I'll just say when it comes to the parties involved
Don't let me directly if possible. Don't interact with them. Don't go into their chats. Don't recap or do commentaries on them
All right. All right, you do have OCD because this is old news
Okay, let's let's talk about what you're gonna do this week and what's okay
I don't I don't I don't want to
give her any acknowledgement.
Okay, I understand.
I understand.
That's one.
That's what fuels her hatred if
you acknowledge her.
She was so nice.
That's the trick.
She did the she did the
Okie doke to me, right?
Okay.
You can tell me what are you
doing this weekend?
Good times.
Well, this weekend, I go walking the woods over at my parents' property and sit in the
forest on a tree stump and listen to the animals running around the birds, listen to
the wind rustle through the trees and.
Yeah, it sounds boring, but it's very peaceful. All right chicken cake says it keeps her going either way
Good times, and I had her going a straight 18 months
Good chicken chicken cakes like sister shit up
I'm a good imagine being a janny. I just unblocked you. I said don't call me a retard
You're now calling me a retard again, and you're saying I don't have ads on you'd like ads
I don't feel like making two cents a month, so I can have the audience who leaves when I even propose my own music
believe when they're
Well, I've had blocker on you can have a you can have scythe thick it thick it. What does that mean?
What are you saying that who puts the thick it Saman
Because hey say a man say say the n word again one time motherfucker
Say it and you can say it in chat say man
You want to say it you spell it with what he's he does. Oh, I know you didn't know how to spell very good very good
But yeah, I mean good Lord people
More hood than any of these motherfuckers. Oh my god
I've run around with Mexican gangs and done some magic for them actually
I've I've I've hung around with the Spanish coverers out of play. I've hung around I've hung around a lot of shit
Yeah, I if we're a same man to think like I live in New York City, you know, I'm a gangster
Okay, we can have a little deep breath. Yeah
And he's gonna pretend he's gonna leave and he's gonna be in here watching like this
You you ban broom gang. I didn't ban broom gang your brother's band or is it clumsy broom gang
They're different. Are they saying that you bang clumsy or I don't know either the broom or clumsy
Look at your the people you ban in your um, yeah, I mean I have I mean literally if you hear these names
Some of these names. It's like is this like the psychopath like class reunion. I mean, it's like I actually put all the names through my
through my, this is going to be on my class chat,
you can see it, I was like,
what do you think about the mental state of these people?
It said they're bad people, basically.
Don't use AI, AI is going to script your brain.
I read an article about three weeks ago,
it says people that extensively use AI,
it's making mentally insane.
Well, I think it already worked on me.
Yeah.
I think I'm already I'm already there. I think everyone's like oh you see how he's up bay clips who actually like you know
You know, it's not it's a kind of creative stuff, but the latest one. He's like, you know, I almost choked
Sorry about this am am talks about how she's a Christian where she wore some Jesus
But what she needs to answer she uses AI and she and I just
She thinks I was not sorry. She thinks AI is God
Oh my god. Well, I see how she uses it. She
She's like a mirror and she'll like she'll do leading questions
I'll just put her transcript through without saying anything
I'll just like let it and analyze and then go
Answer what it thinks of what she said, but she like will say well
What do you think about a demon worshipping 44 year old white man?
Worshipping the devil
Kills children and it's like well that person sounds like he might need some help
I mean, of course, but you're leading that you're putting leading questions
I mean it's ridiculous I've been Debbie for twice have you ever been dead?
Have I been dead? Yeah, I I'd almost died a couple times as a baby. No, I'm not I'm not talking about almost being dead
I've been dead twice. Okay. Yeah, I haven't been like at one time
I drank a floor cleaner thought it was apple juice and my brother found me like
like vomiting on the floor like upside down and
Brammy to like get my son pumped I almost died then and I also had a something with my esophagus
Where I would almost choke to death, right? And and it projectile bomb at everything
I've been in self-induced commas for multiple days.
All right, and I've been dead.
I've seen the afterlife.
There's nothing there.
It's a black void that you float around in.
Well, I like the black void,
but the black void I go to, like when I go to sleep.
It's like, I just want to be in darkness,
but then I start. No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm telling you about when you're getting rated
past the afterlife.
That's DMT, but DMT comes out and.
Well, when you before you really die it does the MT is releasing your brain. That's when a large amounts of it or release
Well, they say they they say that it does happen. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, and my dad
Passed away a couple years ago, but he started like
Recipes, yeah, yeah
He was a good guy, but he started calling for him. Oh, no now beat is gonna go live make fun
You're dead father. Well, you know what?
That's just sick. I mean, it's like I I have never talked about her mother
I never I never I but I remember on Mother's Day when I went to like dinner with mine
Like she was mad that I went to dinner like she's like why is he like leaving the stream to go to dinner on mother?
I mean, it's like I don't know it was like the weirdest they I was like what when is mother days this year
I got remembered. It's on May 6 7th. It's like, you know
No, that's okay. Hey, he man, you used to be a mod and and then I asked you several times to stop badmouthing me other chats and you wouldn't and that's why you're not a mod anymore, but you are welcome in the chat, but let my leave my mom.
So I can tell you a death is it's a black void where you're floating and there's no but you know here's what I think. I think when you get to the black void.
little colors start to appear too.
And then you're like.
No, there's nothing.
It's nothingness.
But you know when you go to sleep
and you go to the black void and then you wake up,
like you always will wake up.
You don't even know.
You don't even know what I'm talking about.
Okay, well, I said, like I said,
I didn't even know the experience of you, baby, okay?
Did my earliest memories
are my dear to nothing experiences?
I don't mean to interrupt, let me talk.
No, I know what I'm talking about,
I put myself in a coma a couple of times and I was close to death.
But look, you've woken up from it.
I wasn't having dreams.
We're having dreams.
Well, sometimes I don't have any dreams.
He didn't let me finish.
You don't want to interrupt, but now you're saying.
I'm sorry.
So it's empty, black void.
They're floating free of thought.
That's what death is.
It was very peaceful. Yeah, because I've been to this I've done shirm and when I did shirm
I went to the sun. You don't even you don't even know what I'm talking about
I do so, you know the sunken place from get out that movie where he's like falling to the black void and he can't like
He's just like can't do anything if they're falling to black. You know, you don't understand. I've tried to kill myself multiple times
I'm sorry
I
I experienced that and God told me I wasn't ready
So in this black boy and you heard a voice
Yes
Tell me more
I that was I had a purpose and I wasn't ready to go
And they say you do have a purpose and you're not ready to go yet
That's cool
Yeah, it's cool. So be alive
You're here for you are for a reason good times, you know, maybe it's even just
To talk to people like me and like, you know, give us some insight. No
Yeah, I just enjoy fucking off. I don't give a shit. Cheers to that. Cheers to that. What are you drinking this morning?
You having a little drink you drink
Well, I'm getting fucked up all day. I'm gonna have a shit
Yeah, I mean it well judge me judge me judge me all you want
I don't fucking judge you. I mean, I listen I drink four very very very strong drinks last night
I I was watching I saw you drinking your twisted iced teas or the hell you drink
I mean, I don't care. I don't
I got drunk in the skunk. I I
was you know what? You know what?
I judge people for what? When
when they hate other people.
Yeah. I don't have you in my
heart. Like even like I get so
hurt that I lash out at people
and stuff. That is a defense
And I just like, give and give my love, I gotta say.
You need to become a little bit more jaded with yours.
I'm getting there, I'm getting there,
when people are making fun of the dead.
Excuse me.
And then saying that I'm making fun of the dead.
When I was actually trying to summon Michael
to hang out with me, because he would always.
Be laughing and always being in a good mood even when he was being like, you know denigrated and made fun of it
Everyone's like constantly harassing
People made fun of me when I when I it was confirmed orange died
And I I did do a stream where I cried about it because we Sam and you've been saying you're leaving for the last at least
Sam and your nigger shut the fuck. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Calm down. He says it
Like ten times straight on your stream
I know but when you say it with that with that Wisconsin accent or whatever
We're bish together in Michigan Michigan. Yeah, and that's all they say then we
Yeah, and he man, are you bothering people in the chat now? Like I mean seriously. He man chill
Okay
Alright, chill out, chill out, chill out, fuckhead.
Calm down, fucking smoke some crack.
Hey man, look, I don't smoke crack.
She's not Tommy James, but...
Well, you got the reference I was surprised you actually caught on
Hey, I'm not I was I didn't just fall off the turnip truck. I'm good times
He man's always been good. Well, is he man? Is he man your mom?
He man's always in my chat and very nice. So he man's a woman. Do you know that he man's a woman good times?
I yeah, well, she's well
In my chat. Yeah
And He-Man is very nice until she's not, and until she's a mod, and then she starts talking shit about me, and other chats and stuff, and like Sam-Man's for example, and saying, oh, say-
Where do you know what that's called? It's called drama farming, you dumbass motherfucker.
See, He-Man, are you drama farming?
Are you a farmer of drama drama farming? I just created up that I just
Farming drama, I just created the term it's gonna spread across the internet
Hey guys, we're gonna spread drama farmers
Villains farm instead of farm bill it's gonna be farm villains. That's I just coined a term to farm villains
No, no, I like drama farming better
She said she's not a farmer well, but farm Billins is kind of like if you're more into the games
And he man has problems too, I mean he man he man talks to talk shit too
Until she's your mod and then goes and talk I don't I don't have any mods. I don't like be my mod. Yeah
I, my chat doesn't, I, you know, I can control my chat on my own.
I don't need to have mods to think that I'm special and like, oh, like, I'm popular.
I don't need fucking mods.
Yeah, but
I mean, it's like you can control your chat and stuff, but I have someone that have a hundred people in chat and there's people skimming.
I'm doing dog, I'm doing dog.
No, no, no, shut the fuck up.
You get a viewbot in, you get a viewbot in, and you have like 10 people in chat and you think there's actually like 126 people watching you know.
I have never viewbotting myself and I was just saying.
You should, no, I'm not saying you do it, but I've had people viewbot me, I don't even know they're doing it.
I'll I'll I'll say there's like 126 people watch me like 200 and whatever there's like 10 people in my chat
Yeah, I know it's not real. Yeah. Well, that happens
I mean Joker would used to view about me once in a while he come on the show all of a sudden there's 100 people
I know he was I know he was I know he was but
And I told them to stop because I don't like because necessarily that good for the it's gonna be dangerous on YouTube
You know because they're not supposed to like inflate your numbers
But there also are lurkers and there's there's hate watchers. Uh, there's not that many lurkers
There's hate watchers. Well, I have a lot of hate watchers. I for example
Beeta c-h-r-a-s-t-i-n-e and other people always seem to have watched every minute of every show
But they're like they never have to say anything in the chat. They're probably watching right now
I have 55 people in chat by the way.
Be the streamer's view about it,
because literally, if I ain't over 100 here,
like 100 people, oh, here's 150 people,
and there's like 10 people.
Show brag about having so many people watching,
and there's like 15 people in our chat, all right?
I mean, yeah, you can actually go,
and there's websites that will show you.
You know what that's called?
That's called an ego trip, all right?
Yeah.
And she's like, and she leads every stream, and she's like, oh, everybody hit the like and stuff.
Why? If you're just going to lead every single stream, you care about how many likes you have.
You know, I don't understand that. And there are cases where I really hate watchers and workers.
Psyche, real talk. I'm not diagnosed with anything mental. Should I ask about it though?
I thought you told me that you are a little bit.
Where are you talking to?
She's not diagnosed with it. Well, I'm not diagnosed with anything, but I think I might be
I am. I've been diagnosed with a lot of shit. It doesn't make me crazy
It makes me a human being that's living.
Hey listen, my school made me go to a psychiatrist
and I was in high school.
And you know what I was diagnosed with in high school?
I visit a psychiatrist every three months.
Yeah, well, I don't,
but in high school they made me go to one and...
What does that make me a flawed human being?
That's my question.
No, I think everybody has something
because they have something called dysthyzmic disorder.
That means...
You don't have anything, but they just have to write something down on the pen because everybody has to have something right there's nothing
I mean are you like you know
Dangerous society no, I don't think no, I'm not guy. I'm not going out and trying to start fights with people
In my pool, I was probably one screwed up sucker Lars. Well, was I I would hit on guys at my school
The teachers didn't like my gay jokes
You know you're getting trolled. I did drugs
They're trying to screw it, you know
Smoked that weed I kind of want to pack another bowl. This is actually just tobacco. I wish it was
Yeah, you're smoking tobacco at bongo because I I smoke these uh swishers and then I say in return to that
And that's all the tobacco and I can't smoke it in my like it's a girl. That's just right
Well, cheers cheers queers. Hey Q does have
Notice that when streamers and turn to a chat. Yeah
Can you just kind of badass, I see.
Nancy, Nancy Joker was looking the other day at Bita.
He put her website onto some site.
It said there was 10 participants and 150.
Robots or something like that. I mean, it's like there's something weird about it
He had a website that actually says these are not real people, but whatever whatever. I don't care
He did know he did I have a short about it, but I take them on my shorts, but yeah, cue or sorry
Joker knows this website where you can plug in this web the the uh
the chat and it will tell you the real people and the robots.
Yeah, there's robots.
They were like, hello, Peter, how are you?
All right.
So did you hear about what Joker did to me?
What did he do to you?
All right, so I did a stream where I knew
my calves get ready to die.
Am I okay not this one?
Oh my gosh.
You know, I was crying live on stream me put on tiktok is the short and
It got 2.3 million views and it was just a bunch of Chinese
No, let's not say I'm sorry about that. That'd be sad
Mouth watering I would fucking knock Joker out with one punch
They're not buts and they're 40 lurkers and real owls
There's real owls
That'd be so crazy if there was owls watching
Like wow
You know my favorite owl is I like those barn owls or barred owls are they called barred owls or barn owls
They had this really pretty face. They're like
But what are they called barred owls or barn owls
Barn owls, they're called barn owls. I thought they're called barred owls. They're crazy. You're crazy. They're crazy. Yeah
No, you're crazy. I
Yeah
You're crazy
Do I look crazy I'm just sitting here you look you look kind of crazy
Called one. You know because I have a beer
Why because I'm under a blanket with a huge neon
Images my name talking to you at eight in the morning on YouTube
Okay, are you jerking off? No
Why why are you laying underneath a blanket? You don't see me with touch my wiener
Well, I'm not even looking at it. Oh, you weren't
No, I'm just kidding. That's the cat in my blink. No, it's not
I'm just kidding it guys. It's all jokes. I
Like to be jerking off right now, but that'd be a little bit too awkward then good times. We be like, what's that?
That's how how do you make the town? Oh my god, what?
That was just my mouth
I swear, good, I swear I'm not jerking, I swear to God I'm not jerking off.
I promise you, okay?
I know I have a sexy voice.
You do, you do.
I love it.
I hardly ever use my normal voice.
I sound like Barry White.
Good times was looking at it. Oh my gosh. Hey, RG leave good times. No, I I can't even I can't even see this
I can't even see my camera because another monitor
Yeah
Well, I mean, I'll take off my also I'll prove that I'm not by taking down my
Background screen and you can look more closely and you'll see that I just
Like to put my hands over my wiener like Michael Jackson to keep it warm
Oh, oh
Good times good times, how are you good times? It's Michael Jackson
Are you okay? Are you okay, sir? Not yet. I need to get this working up
We're gonna for what?
Um, so you talk about how you're a homosexual all the time you can find a boyfriend
You can't find a boyfriend. I can find a boyfriend. Do I want a boy? Yeah? Yeah, how much?
Come on come on come on. Like you're proud of being homosexual. I don't care about I don't know
I don't even like gay sex. I barely like gay people. I mean, they're they're so catty and bitchy and stuff
So what you're saying is you you're um, you're a grifter
You're saying you're a grifter?
No, I'm actually a real gay, but I have...
I don't take so because you said you don't want to find a boyfriend.
Well, not everyone wants a boyfriend.
Listen, I call a bullshit what I call it.
Boyfriends are a headache.
Do you want a girlfriend? Why doesn't he have a girlfriend? You're straight.
Can't you find a girlfriend? Why didn't she get Alexander March?
I can find a girlfriend.
Get Alexander pregnant and your hand have a ball.
But when she wanted to do that
Because she's insane
Okay, good point good point
So how are we going to I don't I don't understand it like I
Remember talking about there night you said you're dying for maids
Was it last night? I didn't ever said that I said if I was
Remember everything everybody said I was dying of AIDS that would be an insult to say I look like I'm dying of AIDS
Yeah
You said you said I'm dying for maize who cares I did not say that good good time you did I
Everything you ever said to me memorize right up here in my computer bank. It looks more like a
balding head
I'm sorry, that was not nice. I'm sorry
Well, yeah
Look at I'm bolding too. You can see look at my look at actually those were where horns used to be
But and okay, and then they're making these memes of me
I have like a ton of beautiful hair on the sides, but they make me bald on top. They gave me a bald mullet
Have you ever heard of such a thing?
What the fuck is that about?
Where is this picture of me? You've only tried to destroy your mind and you don't realize it. Well, there's exceeding
You're a fucking idiot
Excuse me
No, you're fucking it. You don't have the clip. He hasn't memorized in his bald head
Papa roach
Yeah, it's a bold
Know you do you do, but have you seen what I look like now? I mean I
Don't I don't look at you because I'm not gay. I know you don't but it's like you know
You still you can still have to see you know if I'm not if I'm jerking off or not
I'll pull it up one second
I'm not jerking off
Maybe I am I have to ask the honest question dude. Do you use Adrol or methamphetamine?
Neither I just had a good night's sleep and fucking I haven't had my coffee even yet
We tell you how my coffee then I'll be really off the rails
But I'm gonna show you it's what sweet pee makes me look like and what Alexander make me
Oh my god, I'm out. Fuck this. Bye. Bye
I have a good one you too. Thank you for being here
I love you. I just don't care about trauma. I know. I know. I do. I do. I care. Why do you, why do you care about it?
Sometimes I feel like I care too much. You know that song?
No, I asked you a question. Why do you care about drama?
Why do you let it feed your soul with negative energy?
Come on.
Look at this. Look at it. She has me with an alien.
I think this is a picture of our time.
No, no, you're deflecting.
Why do you feed a negative energy and fucking let it feed your soul?
Probably for attention and love.
But look what she made me look like.
Negative energy is not love, motherfucker.
That's a good point. Look at this. Look at this. No, look at me with the
Look it see my hair, that's my hairline right there. You see who's this alien is that Alexandra
Look at me getting hit in the head with a biscuit that never happened in real life
Maybe it happened a couple times. I got in a food fight
I didn't die, it's that I got killed with a biscuit,
that is false advertising.
There's me under my blanket,
but it makes me look like I'm peeking
through somebody's window.
There's just me peeking through my blanket saying hello.
How insulting.
Look, look at me there,
almost dying choking on my Big Mac.
Let's see what else I have.
Let's see, Sweet Pea was here,
let me see what we have here.
When people die they have a party
If they can get the ashes sometimes they'll ask for the ashes they'll smoke them
They'll smoke them in their weed
You never heard of smoking I mean guys it gets sick. It's really sick
They'll say oh, I was their friend. Can I have a little bit of the ashes and they'll smoke them
You didn't hear about that. Why it's in every rap song. What is going on?
What is happening?
I I feel I feel stupider than KZ right now
Yes, you Mars is in your pants move kitty move kitty Mars is in your underwear
It is
Far as I know I just speak from the heart
I'm also a psychic and I pick up these thoughts when people die
It's true. So you haven't seen any of any of that stuff on on caps lately. It's like you haven't watched any of that
I haven't what he's talking about
Huh, but what like they're you're like, you know making stuff up. I almost died
About me and and and that's how and basically getting using Shannon to go like a basically
Oh
Are you good? I almost died. Oh god out of your conflict growing up. I don't want to sound like it
I ate too much Big Bag at once.
Sorry.
Look at that, I almost died.
Oh my God.
This is comedy for people.
I'm fine.
Sick.
I took my Big Bag.
My favorite, Dynamique Nagy.
Happy birthday, Josh.
Where's the post?
All the posts are gone.
What happened?
Is that by the wrong page or something?
Hold on.
Sweepie was here.
Where?
She took him all down.
Why would she take all the posts down?
This is not there. I am I don't understand anyway. Well, she's taking down all the posts
Yeah, the wig
Now poor wig
That was being cobra. Yeah, he died. I mean, it's like what's your bully of him?
I know he was getting bullied. What if she was his bully like his worst bully?
Can you imagine that and she's responsible for his death?
About that. I did it two seconds later. I went and breath. Happy birthday, Josh. Where's the post all the post?
Oh, everything is about money for you. Yes, it is
I look great
Okay. It looks great.
We're actually really nice people.
Okay.
I got a little bit excited.
What is that?
Yeah, the police say come to the door because I don't laugh.
What do you think of you?
What?
Ba-da-ba-ba-ba.
Your job, which is saving lives.
It's a pretty fucking discussion.
I'm sorry.
I'm talking to you right now, by the way.
Sorry.
Okay, cool.
Oh, you're watching me.
You're watching me.
You know, him coming up and joining at least to be like two persons to invest because not your job, which is saving lives. It's a pretty fucking
Oh my god
To be a tarot card reader, right
people? Yes. Is that what you're projecting for people? I mean, seriously?
Maybe IP two will pick him up because that's that he's now
you want to be
No, I don't, I don't actually, I don't.
It's funny because I've been on Vita's channel and her and Sweet Pea are just super rude and weird to me and trolled me.
I'm funny, I'm funny.
I'm saying go right, like you know the difference?
Just because you have a real life brain in front of you doesn't mean it's working.
Not bad.
Mr. Sandman, porn bomb my stream, put up a graphic of vagina and peen.
I'm funny
Not these are funny. I'm funny. Then it's a you're heard like a big retard
Be charred
I mean, I mean dumb bitch in Farsi
This is why if you see really, oh, I want to you're really like cuz you're not like that AI photo you're using bitch, okay?
Okay
This is where the people can see like what you're really like you too one time. I did shoplift like a huge thing of
Pistachio
Like I could have gone for like the like a little bag of pistachios, but I went for like the five-pound bag
And this huge thing of pistachio nuts
This is a few years ago. Okay. This is guys. I don't recommend doing that. You're hungry. I was hungry
I walked out of the store and I got and the lady lady
I don't know if she worked there something but she's she started screaming that I had a pistachio
So I started running on the street. It's huge bag of pistachio nuts in my pants
That was embarrassing to
The police don't
I need a bit fried so many came through for me and they're reading and everything. Hey psyche in Canada
You can't buy anything for five dollars. I said five. I didn't say anything about ten. Why are you dumb? Oh?
They said poutine
It's just lying to stir it off. It's weird. I am funny right? What's this one? Yeah, right? Oh
My god, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. But yeah, guys, we're gonna be funny though
I'm so sorry. I had a book
Sweet pea that did that never happened. It never happened. Okay
Sweet pea. You and me. Bye, man. Have a better day, okay?
Sweet pea. We're going to be the new BKG. We're going to keep you out of it.
This isn't you and me. We're in polygons. We're in play with you.
Okay. Oh, oh, oh. No, I didn't mean to do this to you.
Do you guys need a ghost pepper? Donate to one of the lollipops?
I do too. I do too. I do too.
Cash apps like to be awakened.
Is sweet pea? We all go to the crazy sometimes.
Jenny girl Jenny. Yeah, go fuck yourself bitch
It's passive aggressive is it passive aggressive like having a whole live about me
You know saying I have please
Get out of here
Okay gang die
What's up motherfuckers? What's up motherfuckers?
Fucking damn it is good. Hey get the fuck out of here. I don't want to talk to you anymore. Bye
What do you want? This is what you want bitch?
We all go to the crazy sometimes
This is a great channel.
Like, I'm lucky that I'm bald and stuff.
If ice comes here, I'm gonna build my family.
That's what Siren said.
I'm clumsy bean gang.
He was saying, hey, Samman has a nice ass.
I was fucked with a guy or I was in jail or something.
I fucked Samman.
And I really like, I wish I had like control of J-Dog.
Like I could, okay, that'd be fun.
Like I could just like, go.
I could just make him a sex slave and stuff but I've always been like bosom buddies, you know
But you know when mine laying on his bosoms and I told her I unblocked boo boo kitty
Which I shouldn't have done but I was like, you know and then
Katie would say well fuck you fuck you sack. You have your cats have fleas. Oh, Alex
They took takes all these cocks and stuff like that. I was like, I know Alex McQueen does as like
You know, we've talked about I pulled him to like, you know cut down a little bit on the on the guy
Like I'm lucky. I'm just not bald and stuff
Vice comes here. I'm gonna build my family. Oh my goodness crazy
So, yeah, you dated Emma for years.
Is that, what do you mean?
No, not for years.
Is that what you are, buddy, buddy, with her now again?
I haven't talked to her in months,
but I introduced you to her.
So why are you giving a fuck about her?
Because by how many years you've been dating her,
I introduced you to her later.
No, no, listen.
I dated her for like a year, 15 years ago.
Oh my god, no.
And she's been going after me for all this time.
She's fucking out of her mind.
Hold on, please.
I'm on their way.
I'm busy.
Sucker and sucka-tash.
Where is it?
You don't call me.
Say that again?
Sucker and sucka-tash?
You just
So yeah, you dated Emma for a year. Hey Ryan Reynolds. Oh, I'm straight shoot by the way. Um, I'm a fake psychic, but I am a real
I'm a straight person because when you assume you make an ass out of you and me, especially you, okay?
But somebody in this world pretend to be gay. I mean, I think this is not the three's company, you know
Where it's like I need to rent a apartment with the you know, two hot women and mr.
Furley or mr.
Roper is gonna be suspicious and the next Ted Bundy. Yeah, I just pretend I'm gay to get sympathy from women
Oh great this spiritual trafficker is kind of bad too. I need to get mental help. I look like the golem. I look like you know
Terrible oh
I'm hungry. I was up the street. You look at like a maniac
Okay, Alex you bitch
Get a refund. I don't care. You're not mad anymore anymore. You suck
I mean, fuck, Kate, I mean, these people, I mean, fuck.
How do I deal with this?
I mean, there's McDonald's, I'll show it.
Oh, I have to show it myself, come on.
I mean, Jesus Christ, no, I'm not lying.
You can have a, Alex, I don't lie.
I'm not gonna say no.
If you didn't get more material,
I'd blame you on the channel.
You got it, I didn't get it.
I've played your whole channel.
Oh!
Oh, well, well, do you want me to eat your pussy?
Saiki, what is wrong with you?
I think, remember when we met, you said you wanted to cuddle with me?
I want to do that still.
Yeah, but that was just a joke, you know, I don't fuck with you.
You said if you were going to pick me up, pick me at Orange County,
we're going to cuddle and negotiate these bands.
Yeah, but that was just, you know, I was drinking the tequila that night.
That wasn't okay.
You know what they say, keep your friends close.
and your enemies.
And sweet tea that bitches closer.
I don't want her closer. It's scary.
She might eat you?
Yeah.
I call her sour piss, actually.
Or sour poo.
I can see this relationship flourishing.
Let it happen.
Arthur, just lay back, close your eyes,
and unzip your pants.
Well, do you want me to eat your pussy?
Spin the chat to sweep spin chat to sweep
Bye Sam and out of my life
Hey, go fuck your kitty gang, die!
Shout to Sweepie!
Spend the day!
Look at all these people that are mods and you're not.
Time, Jamie's Cowboys.
The shit sandwich, that was Sweepie.
That was Sweepie.
And that was because I said, you know,
Christine called me a scumbag and I'm like,
Christine, um,
like your, um,
like your face,
Your material needs some some work and some extensive work, you know, and it's getting old and
Fat scarecrow Samman. I'm on block 3b. Don't bless the woman. She took time
I will like to make fun of you and me and this oh, she's like
Thank you, Samman. Oh
He's like beta beta beta. Let me talk please please. He's like please let me talk
She's like no
Didn't say anything Sam that wasn't me
That was my handlers
Look at all these people that are mods, and you're not time
People talk to me like everybody and then what is what does he say? Oh go eat a shit sandwich? I mean
What the fuck what in the fucking fuck I got a lady I mean
She's been abducted by aliens like the real Alexandra. This is not her. I mean, what the fuck?
How did I get brought into this shit?
What the f**k are you saying? I'm bald?
I mean, they have one picture of me with like a...
I mean, my hairline is weird in places, right?
I'm not bald.
She'd be like, oh my god, you're going bald.
I'm not bald, I have nice hair.
But you're still like, ah!
Ow!
Oh my god, the end.
What's up motherfuckers?
Do you have a problem?
I'm naked and naked for you.
Don't even we're seriously this way here. I'll go crazy tonight here Jenny girl sucks
Jenny girl Jenny and go fuck yourself bitch
Go to hell
Boxers, that's how ski man
But
Here there you go
We all go to the crazy sometimes
Okay, get out of here big time. Get out of here. You're BAD! BAD!
I thought it said D-I-D-D-L-E-R.
What's up motherfuckers? What's up motherfuckers?
You have a problem? You have a problem?
I'm making it for you.
She wasn't even more seriously this way I heard
She does not take you seriously. You're not a terror card reader. Look at how you're acting
He's convulsing
I bet.
Look who went live.
We know you've been in Emma's chat under all stream.
I barely even know that bitch's name anymore.
Emma who?
That's what I'm gonna say.
I'm not in that bitch's chat.
She's not interesting.
She's not even a good terror reader, okay?
I know.
I just thought it was kind of a word.
I didn't like the word.
A mod?
Mods?
I'm sorry.
Get him out of here.
Can you just?
Why am I picking on Fred, Clem?
I'm about to pick on you.
Emma, you're a fucking succubus.
That's what you do.
So you do is all you do is drain energy from people and you're proud of it
I mean, it's like what are you talking about? That seems harsh. I'm a little Clem
You know once you're on your own show you can make those decisions for yourself. Okay, oh
Look at Fred Levi-ton to have a friend Levi-ton have a friend Levi-ton to a hundred
You're gonna be banned over and over again, and it's not a big deal. So bye
We look who went live. We know you've been in Emma's chat under all
You have to be careful with the head buns, you do have to be careful with the head buns.
Sorry.
There you have two left.
I'm sorry, how do I look guys?
Do I look like a ponytail?
Do I look 45?
My ponytail as well.
Hey!
Yeah!
I don't know anything about the Spirits of Trafficker!
Who called you anything?
Nobody.
You need to stop.
You need to stop doing it.
Stop.
Stop what?
I'm not the Spirits of Trafficking anybody else!
I don't work for PETA!
What are you just talking about?
She's here everyday.
Yeah, I was trying to kidnap her for PETA or something like that.
I don't know, I don't even know this one.
She looks like PETA's.
She got PETA's every day.
What do you mean?
I don't know if she's going to get mad at me.
I really don't appreciate it.
world. Hey, yeah, there were 86 people. I'm here with like two people. So obviously,
everyone fucking hates me. I mean, I guess I'm even like, not like people can't come back and
forth or something. No, just like 90 people, three people here. Like, everyone just hates me.
It's kind of depressing thought. I mean, guys, it's really
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bells Jingle Bell
You're banned from the studio. You're banned. You're banned. Get out.
Jingle bells, jingle bells.
If you have to pang, uh...
No prizes on my draw.
Ooh, what it is? Can you, can you go take the camera?
Oh, look at this. Oh, here.
Here's this.
Here you go.
Aww.
What? What was it? Show me. Show me fucking. Show me. Show me. What is it? Come on. Show
me, Papa. Show me. Let the content, content. Let me see.
Like, open it up. Open it up. It's in a bag. Open it up. Let's see. Open it up.
This is disgusting.
Open it up.
Remember?
Are you crying?
I'd rather have dead mice than alive ones.
Holy s***, listen.
Hey, Louis, what's up?
Hello.
I love it.
Creepy has a post on her wall that says,
I found out I was gifted a cult of psyche membership.
She said she started punching the air.
She was so mad.
She said, you know what she said?
She said she likes being in a psyche haters club.
I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, I
No one's gonna, no one's gonna bother you about that $800. I hope you left it too. I hope you left it to Mirna
and she's she's spending on some fucking handbags
Geez
Okay, I'm officially a fan of her channel now
Officially I
Think I like that person. I'm so sorry. I didn't I didn't know I was so funny. I
Had no idea. Okay. Now. Let me get to the Alexandra
It's to say you know what sadder they're gonna be timed out. Oh
Okay, so I'm gonna read the Alexandra um transcript right now, okay, I have it I have it all ready
Yeah, Sam and go cry it about the wrench and go cry about you got time to come on a Air Force Sam's gonna come in a second
And he's gonna see like what you've been me Pappas
Yeah, I don't want the content killer here
Sam all Sam I want to do is
Literally play three hours of music requests and then six hours of big trollah doing her eyeliner and mate and lips
I'm like, what is this?
What am I watching and
Then I'll come on the panel and then all of a sudden beat is there. Christine's there. We're all fighting
10 seconds later
And then it's back to a big troller doing her makeup
For another two hours, I mean it's like
And there's over a hundred people in the room
What in the fucking fuck like literally I'm not I wish I was just like this was a joke
This is what it literally is
I was like who's this what is this a makeup tutorial channel?
It's just this kind of like woman just doing lipstick and putting eyeliner on and whining about life. I
Don't understand. I don't I don't understand the history of it
Hey, Amanda. How are you sweetheart? I just don't understand. I don't know the lore. I don't know the big troll of lore, I guess, right?
Yeah
And I'm just like sitting there like okay, my middle finger's been up for at least like 10 seconds after the countdown
When am I gonna be kicked off the show? I mean, I can I think I can still have the interview
I mean, I should have just been talking.
I could have gotten every single point I had at.
He's so slow.
You just, you just press kick.
It takes two seconds or literally less.
It takes, I kick people up and half a second.
You do a countdown and I'm sitting there
with my middle finger up for like at least like a 60 second.
I don't understand.
I just don't get it.
I don't know if I'm right for this world.
And that's not, I don't want to hear the nine, eight, eight.
I don't want, okay, it's this bigger speech, okay?
Yeah, shout out to the shout out to the shout out
Stop shouting everyone out my ears are hurting stop shouting out
He never shouts me out. He never says. I'm fucking his content for half the time
He never says shut up to suck it. Yeah, he says. Oh you crack head you crack head
I sound like a crack kid Samar I sound like a crack kid
SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY SORRY S
Well, I'm going to read the Alexander Mayer's transcript about me trafficking for pebs and
zayno.
Okay, don't go into the chats, don't recap or do commentaries on them.
While I do my commentary on him right now, but don't you don't do it.
Just me, just me.
Just I'm allowed to do it because I'm Alexander Mayer's because realistically their viewership
is very minute.
Not like my, not like my chat where there's two people and nobody commenting.
like psyches where there's 50 people at seven in the morning and everyone's laughing and having a good time.
Right? Oh, I'm sorry. Maybe I maybe I elaborate on that transcript a little bit. Okay. Um,
it looks like a lot of people, but it's not. It's a very small viewership. It's the same exact
audience going from one party within the group of people that we're talking about today to the other
party, to the other party. Well, it's because it's a party, not a boring snooze-fes-a-year show, woman.
They're not popular streamers. No, we're not popular
Just 50 people in the chat of 55 people in the chat at 919 on Monday morning
It's nothing really. It's just nothing really, right?
They try to present it like they are but they're not nobody cares about them
You guys don't care about me
You don't care about me
I thought you cared
Oh
Oops, I just banned something. I'm so sorry
They try to present it like they are but they're not nobody cares about them
And nobody should be surprised that they're essentially teamed up. I
Called this like a month or two ago. You must be a psychic woman when I noted that demon promoter
Stop calling Lilith a demon
She has her bad days
She's usually
Pleasant when I meet her my dreams
She's beautiful. She loves to comb her hair. Sometimes it's red. Sometimes it's black. She's gorgeous
She doesn't look like that monster you put on her. She's gorgeous woman. She's not like some
You know, you make her look like like hellboy or something like that. She's not
It's offensive
And I noted that demon promoter who I said is a fraudulent
Psychic and definitely is somebody who is um mentally a oh
Is this the pot calling the kettle black?
No, you're mentally stable.
I think everyone knows I'm the mentally ill one
and you're mentally stable.
If I'm crazy, it's because you and Bita made me crazy, okay?
I was, have you seen my picture from six months ago
where I look like a prince?
But when I noticed that he was putting together
a new wiki for these live streaming communities,
I bet you he's building that wiki specifically for primary parties outlined on rumored and
I don't like that word said.
Why would you have that website?
Of course that domain was available because nobody is insane enough to have a website
name that except for you.
Okay.
But it's okay.
Well, let's continue.
And I was correct because the only reason that they could want to communicate with him
Would be because of what he can do for them, which is a form of decalculation that they can actually use to leverage to slander people
To blackmail people to explore. Okay
again
This is your playbook though slander
blackmail exploit extort
Isn't that I learned it from watching you Alexandra. I learned it from watching you
That's what that wiki which now they be calling a codex is actually
It's just an extortion and blackmail mechanism.
Okay, all it is, is a fucking website
with my transcripts on it and links to my shows.
Hello? I mean, is there anything...
One person that's gonna get blackmailed and extorted
is me from this website.
I'm giving away too much of my information, but...
I mean, good lord.
It's a it's a simple codex. What because I put a fun
I didn't want to call it wiki because all of a sudden I'll have the wikipedia people suing me
So I named it codex now. I might have chat GPT sewing me
Side talkie to talkie souls
That's not how you spell to talkie. He's about sh i t a k e should talkie. It's a kind of mushroom
Don't take your soul damn it
I'm gonna suck that soul out of your dick so fast your head's gonna spin like the exorcist
How about that Papa's
Okay, okay, okay
Jimmy Joe you mean Jenny Jones, and she's not
Jimmy Jones
No, I called him Jimmy. They called him James Jones or Jim Jones not Jimmy Jones
It sounds like the Jenny Jones talk show that Jenny Jones's brother. He never had he was less popular
Oh my god, there's a spider in the room! There's a spider in the room!
Ugh! Ugh!
I'm gonna get my vacuum cleaner and my toilet. Ready.
Papas?
It's not Kool-Aid. It's more of a crystal light.
It's called crystal light. Not Kool-Aid.
Kool-Aid has too much sugar in it for me.
I like...
I like... or Kate got me onto this Starburst and Skittles flavored juice.
That shit's good.
Tastes like candy, but it's like without the you don't get the cavities just taste. It's just like that like kind of the candy taste
Don't drink the Kool-Aid Mrs. Jones
The devil of Miss Jones. Are you talking about salmon that porno was from the 1970s? What are you watching?
But the next thing is Debbie does Dallas, right?
These are on beta max cassette tapes
You know, there's new porno's have come out since them
I know, it's great, Amanda.
You know, there's new points have come out
since the devil, Mrs. Jones, the Green Door
and Debbie does Dallas.
There's actually really good, like you put VR headsets on
and you're all of a sudden in a black gang bang.
It was the best day of my life, literally.
Double penetration.
Guys spitting and choking everybody. It's great
Love it. I
Don't have any water. I just have some alcohol. Oh my god, my alcohol is local
The cult of pussy. Oh
You're spelling with my name. I'm sorry. Oh my gosh, my name spells pussy. I
Think I might need to rebrand
The Cult of Pussy?
Shit.
Fuck.
What have I done?
Pussy Awakens. Oh, here's my nose. Isn't that great?
You mean, oh, you mean the nails my nails are all hammered in don't call me a loser
Chris Benoit the family man, did you know what Chris Benoit did I'll shave I'll need a hundred dollar donation for a shave
Senate to cash up psyche awakens, please right now, and I'll shave on the show. I'll shave my pussy. I
Mean my vagina, I mean my my wiener
What?
What's that word? What?
Hey, I want to wrestle with you Chris Benoit, but don't bring the knives if you know what I mean
Can I wrestle with you
Hey, Sam and I'm talking to Chris Benoit right now get the fuck out of here
I thought I banned you 10 minutes ago. You said you were leaving at least two hours ago
You're still here
You can't take your eyes off me. You love me. He loves love me
I look like a love stick stalker.
Yes, Mina, please. Please. Yes, Mina.
You want to play with me, RG? You want to come out and wrestle with me? Let's do it.
Oh my God, my pants.
Ready? I'm going to get my wrestling single.
I can't afford a manicure right now.
Stop what? Someone found me to a wrestling match
Chris Benoit
Why what?
We're going to Christine's Christie. Nobody goes to Christine's
How would you go there? You're oh you want to sleep when you want to fall asleep. Yeah, I mean she'll play some trivia. Oh
What what is the capital of Ohio?
Cleveland. Is that Cleveland? Maybe not. I don't have chicken legs. Oh
That just came out, let's look up
Guys, it's not easy being this funny and what where is there? Oh look at the cash apps rolling in
I'm fucking the funniest person I've ever heard of my life and
Sweepy is making more money off of my content than I am. This is disgusting
Sweepie has a more popular channel than I do and it's me
It's my channel. I
Have big brothers, but they want to beat me up. So I can't really
Really talk to them right now
Yeah, no, it's a isn't it sick isn't the world at a weird place. Oh
Let's go to sweepies channel of just it's just shorts of my show. I'm here. I
Know not every joke lands, but I mean Jesus, cry many
It's messed up. It's fucked up. I'm sad. Can someone send me a dollar just to say hey
Don't give up on life and look you know stay stay because you're literally making
46 people laugh and have a good morning, but you're not rewarded. No one cares
Let's go donate to Sweet Peas channel. Let's do that instead
It's okay. I'm poor too because of this show. I'm poor too. I understand what you're I understand it should be should be
I'm poor too because of this show
I'm sitting here with my literally my pants are down
That I mean that's how much I'm dedicated to this stupid bit of wrestling with Chris Benoit
Who is actually dead because he killed himself in his family?
Okay, that got dark a little bit. I'm sorry
Shit
I'd love to do a tarot reading, but I've been a rule.
I'm not gonna do a tarot unless I'm asked,
because you don't show something right.
That's not what the ten of wands means, eh.
Hello, hello.
I know what the ten of wands means.
Hello, I've been doing tarot literature
since I was eight years old.
Eh, eh, eh.
I know I do need a manager, but please be careful with the N word right there. You saw it when you saw the name. It's sad
I'm sad too
Why don't you send me five bucks and ask for a reading and I'll fucking do a reading?
But now you're just gonna like say oh, you're sad. I know I'm sad
No one's fucking buying a reading. Oh
Oh
I mean, I do my, I mean, I go through my poetry book and pick a page and read it for half an hour in Barcy.
But your readings are shits like you when you're like just fast and and tell the exact thing, right?
I don't know. I don't know. This world doesn't make sense to me anymore.
I know Nick, Nick, I am familiar.
But first of all until I get the license, I will get arrested
Every clip oh
I mean a tripping tripping kick is making more money on me on rumble that I'm making off my show
It's just purely my show. Just the whole thing. I
Mean, I don't really mind because then I can like, you know delete my episodes and still catch them later and laugh
Thank you loser. I appreciate it
mean guys you can watch me be hilarious dirty nails are no I know my nails
aren't always perfect you can watch beta is talking a high-pitched voice to a
bunch of weirdos including me okay I'm there too sometimes you can listen you
can watch Sam and makeup tutorials big troller and I wouldn't I think she needs
doesn't look that great. I mean I've seen people with makeup tutorials like whoa
that mean it's like she's even doing makeup tutorial just doing her makeup
I'm really confused. She looks the same after she does it and stuff except with
little darker lipstick and maybe some eyeliner and stuff. It's Sam and she just
and two hours of terrible music donations.
While I make fun of Psyche playing three minutes
of the original song that he wrote,
you can with the assistance of AI
for the graphics and the music.
And Psyche will be called a horrible things
and then everyone will be licking my butthole,
about a Sandman or Bita.
My butthole is unfortunately very dry.
No one's really looking at it, my chat is so evil to me.
Saman!
Mr. Saman, start a new stream, play five hours of music.
That makes me wanna cream.
I need to work on the lyrics a little bit.
And then, Beeta will come...
Well, I'm... Q, I just have to try everything.
And are you giving me advice about streaming Q?
Q.
Don't. Don't even start.
Okay, I'm gonna continue the Alexander Mayer's epic.
Don't tell me how to cheat my chat.
My chat loves it when I abuse them. They love it.
They abused me it's a it's a it's a very toxic relationship, but I love it
Okay, so now the wiki which they're calling a codex is actually it's an extortion in blackmail mechanism
But um, yeah, that's a little bit of a big um, okay. Let's continue the transcript
Nobody should be surprised that they're publicly communicating and essentially working together at this point
I mean this has been something that a horrific mother who got arrested for methamphetamine use a woman notice
AMBER. She's been working on this, getting these parties together for a long time.
Yes, we just had a big meth party. I've never even met Amber. I love Amber. I've talked to her.
We're in the same chats and stuff. What is this methamphetamine cult I want to join?
But no, there's no meth. My cult is not even real.
I'm trying to get something together with pebs and pebs and zaya in las vegas
All I want to do is sit in the corner and watch I said too much shit
Okay, shut up. Okay, the name of her name game is some in it manufacture lawsuits against people same
Well, she has not sued me yet, but you've threatened to
This is projection 101 same goes for the woman who was involved in animal abuse adult content
Along with I don't this is getting disgusting along with multi-guy interracial gang bangs
Again, is this projection?
Didn't I watch you get banged by two white guys on a tennis court in a 19 era 2012
Film and didn't I see you play mrs. Huckstable in a really disappointing porno
About the Cosby show
Why was that made?
Oh, and you're proud. I played the Felicia Rashad role in, you know, Bill Cosby fucked
me in the butt. This is getting disgusting. I can't even finish this. I mean, this is
just disgusting. You can go read the transcript yourself.
The fuck, I mean, Raging Demon, I wish I was kidding.
She played the Felicia Rashad role.
I'm gonna look it up, hold on.
Let's see what the game's called.
Cosby came in my mouth, hold on, one second.
Cosby show, porno.
Starring Monica Foster as Rudy Huxbaugh.
Okay, hold on one second.
No, Monica Foster, okay.
Yeah, the Cosby show, it says parody.
Without getting my channel seriously restricted
It's called the Cosby show. I mean that's not a very creative name
You could think at least come to come up with something more original. What kind of shit is that?
You're at your tail you're asking me I'm on a date with this woman and she's talking about I
Played Felicia Rashad in the Cosby show porno
But she didn't get an AVM. Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
But she did a great. I don't know Claire. I think it's no Claire huckstable Claire huckstable. I'm sorry
I mean, I'm not trying to be funny. This is just my life isn't putting pops more involved
There are pills in the pudding
Yellow pudding. Yellow pudding. How does he say it?
Yellow pudding. He sounds so happy when he says it.
Yellow pudding pops.
I like a pudding pop.
May I have one?
I don't want one that's been put into a vagina or a butt.
I'd like a fresh pudding pop with the wrapper on it, please
I don't trust food coming out of your refrigerator. That's unwrapped
You heard about that in her specific video you heard about okay, so you've heard of the Cosby show video, but she's saying oh
Well amber did a gang bang or whoever. I don't know I don't know. I'm sorry
I maybe wasn't amber
Amber's the head of the methamphetamine cult. It gets so confusing. It gets so confusing
Nothing gets my hot dog harder than some classic. Oh, yeah, your hot dog. Can I see your hot dog?
Can I see your wiener?
Q?
Please.
Okay, I have to go. So now why are you making that face?
Wow, that's an emoji right there that it's like this. I've never even seen that color and it's making a face of
Disgust disappointment and regret and all at the same time. What is that emoji called? Is that the Zalgo?
Is that called Zalgo?
Look and Q's getting laughs for saying the word hot dog
I'm literally
Doing impressions of the entire Cosby
It's okay. It's okay. I'm gonna quit
The first comedic porno, I think Debbie does Dallas was kind of funny
I don't know if it was trying to be but I'm hilarious too. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Theo Huckstable
Yeah, but we can't talk about his scenes. There's there's some cool. Yes
Very the labyrinth is like one of my favorite movies. You remind me of the babe. What babe the babe with the power
What power power of voodoo who do you do what?
remind me of the babe
I saw my baby
Crying hard as a baby could cry. What could I do?
My baby gone so long and left my baby. Oh my god, blue. Nobody knew.
What kind of magic spell to use?
Frogs and males, puppy dog tails, thunder and lightning.
And baby said,
Ha ha ha, dance magic, dance magic, dance magic, dance magic.
Put that magic spell on me.
Jump, magic, jump, magic, jump.
He had a breath.
Do it easy. Yeah. Hey, Massey. Hey, here's my David Bowie impression
Hold on
Okay, I've got too much. Okay, I should I've been a mystery. I'm gonna add a breath. Whoo
Hmm
Ziggy start us. Yeah
I'm gonna pull my pants. I'm sorry. This is embarrassing. I think I embarrassed myself
Anything for a laugh psyche anything for a laugh
Excuse me. Hold on. Give me a second.
And he married, he married a man. David Bowie married a man. Her name was actually I am,
A-N, a man. I mean, Iman. Iman. He married, Iman. He married, he was, he married a, a, a, a reggae person.
Samans give me hearts. Labyrinth is a classic.
Hello, Jerry. Hello, Jerry.
Can you just remember that lady with the, the, the, she,
I didn't carry everything in my bag.
I remember this lady.
Hi, sweetheart.
I remember that lady.
Her name was like the junk lady.
Cause she didn't sell meth.
She just had a junk on her bag.
And she was like, hello, Jerry. Hello.
Ah, the trash lady. Hello, hello now.
Look, I have Mr, Mr. Bear.
Remember your name, Mr. Bear?
Oh, and here's lady the baby doll. I mean, it's like and wait a second. This isn't real
This isn't real. This is all junk. It's all junk. I
Just have like a literal, you know Muppet animatronic walking you's rocking through a junkyard with my house in it
But I think this is real
Yeah, I'm sorry guys
Sorry
What am I gonna do with myself? What are we gonna do Trixie? What are we gonna do?
What are we going to do I love you
Thing that is
You give me kissy
Good times is betraying me why where is he he starts his own stream
Christine's panel she has a panel
Never been invited there
Guys let's do a raid of Christine's panel, but I want
You to troll her heavily okay
But everyone go what's her channel name can someone so her channel name?
And I'll end my stream and then say psyche rated your channel. I want 40 people in there
I want Christine's bikini top to blow off. She's so shocked
Can we do that can someone post her channel name and then I'll end the stream
Is it Christine Diaye? Can't from the opera?
The Phantom of the Opera is there
inside your mind
The Phantom of the Opera
I don't can't go that high as it really is. No, you don't want to do it really. You can go troll her. It's fun
You don't want to see your bikini top blow off?
That'd be quite a that'd be that'd be quite a clip
I want to see her bikini top blow off and then those those those 80-year-old pepperonis
Getting puckered up you're sick psyche. Thank you. You're sick
And
Okay, there's her live guys. Let's go troll the fuck out of her. Okay
There's her link right there
Everyone get the channel. Let's go troll her
Get her the first of all say you're being rated by psyche and second of all we want to see your top blow off. I
Mean, but I'm gonna end I'll be back
Yeah, we want we want we want to blow off her top
Yeah
No, you can be nice, but but your trolls, right?
Isn't aren't this the troll community? What's it? Why are you looking so sad?
Why is it why is saying that is making that face I haven't seen these emojis I've never seen such sad emojis in my life
Well, I mean hey, she's playing trivia with good times and one other person I'm a god
She's she's over there with good times and be to probably doing a trivia game with nobody in the chat. Let's go
Pop her top off. I don't know. Well, it'll be fun. I'll be over there, too
I want to see how long it takes me to get banned. Okay, I'm actually just doing her favor and stuff and subscribe to her channel
Dude, she's not a bad lady. She's just kind of a bitchy bitch sometimes. Okay. I'll talk to you soon
Hey guys, I love you
It will go to shit. I got it. Oh, I promise
But it'll be fun to see her reaction
Okay, I'll see you there
Wow